Guide to the Shaun Maloney Papers
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- Shaun Maloney papers, 1932-2000; 5255-001; 35.08 cu. ft. (37 units); 261 sound cassette tapes; 10 videocassettes (VHS); 1 sound tape reel; 7 sound cassette tapes (microcassettes)
  Correspondence, minutes, speeches and writings, ephemera, publications, photographs, tape recorded interviews and interview transcripts, video tapes, clippings, and numerous other materials resulting from his friendships with other labor activists; 1932-2000. Includes records of his various union affiliations, including the Teamsters, 1947-1996; Sailors Union Of The Pacific, 1935-1955; International Longshoremen's And Warehousemen's Union, 1937-1998; and International Longshoremen's And Warehousemen's Union Local 19, 1962-1975 (bulk).
  Open to all users.
  Estate of Shaun Maloney c/o Dallas Delay, Seattle, Washington.
  - Personal Papers
    - Biographical Features, 1942, 2000 (Box-folder 1/1-3)
    - General Correspondence
      - Abella, Ampora "Maria", 1949-1950 (Box-folder 1/4)
      - Almeida, Arthur and Irene, 1965, 1973-1997, n.d. (Box-folder 1/5)
      - Anderson, James E. and Dee, 1953-1955, n.d. (Box-folder 1/6)
      - Bailey, Bill and Michael, 1989, 1995, n.d. (Box-folder 1/7)
      - Barbara, Frank, 1957 (Box-folder 1/8)
      - Bayspoole, Sam, 1950, 1980-1984 (Box-folder 1/9)
      - Bogle and Gates, 1959, 1985 (Box-folder 1/10)
      - Bowen, Jim B., 1965 (Box-folder 1/11)
      - Breitman, George and Dorothea, 1980-1982, 1989, n.d. (Box-folder 1/12)
      - Brodsky, Arthur, 1953, 1962 (Box-folder 1/13)
      - Brown, Archie, 1974-1977, 1989, n.d. (Box-folder 1/14)
      - Brown, Robert J., 1982 (Box-folder 1/15)
      - Bull, Tas and Carmen, 1974 (Box-folder 1/16)
      - Burke, Eddie, 1995, n.d. (Box-folder 1/17)
      - Burton, Leigh, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 1/18)
      - Business Service Checklist, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 1/19)
      - Butler, Lester, 1951 (Box-folder 1/20)
      - Carlson, Gilbert, 1940-1942 (Box-folder 1/21)
      - Carpenter, Earl and Nettie, 1942-1945 (Box-folder 1/22)
      - Casey, Robert (Bob), 1960 (Box-folder 1/23)
      - Castle, Del, 1997 (Box-folder 1/24)
      - Caughlin, John, 1985 (Box-folder 1/25)
      - Chan, Betty, 1949-1951 (Box-folder 1/26)
      - Christian, Richard J., 1947-1962, 1986, n.d. (Box-folder 1/27-29)
      - Coleman, Carl A., 1964, n.d. (Box-folder 1/30)
      - Connelly, Pat, 1965 (Box-folder 1/31)
      - Conway, Steve, ca. 1986 (Box-folder 1/32)
      - Coover, Oscar, 1943 (Box-folder 1/33)
      - Cote, Phillip and Marie, 1959-1982, n.d. (Box-folder 1/34-35)
      - Cummins, Dick, 1965 (Box-folder 1/36)
      - Curcio, Jim, 1962 (Box-folder 1/37)
      - Davenport, Harry T., 1953-1984, n.d. (Box-folder 1/38-42)
      - Dean, C.W., 1978 (Box-folder 1/43)
      - Dean, James, 1986 (Box-folder 1/44)
      - DeBoer, Harry and Pauline, 1962-1992 (Box-folder 1/45)
      - DeGraff, John, 1981 (Box-folder 1/46)
      - Delay, Dallas, 1980-1998, n.d. (Box-folder 1/47)
      - DeMarco, Donald (Tony), 1949, 1965, n.d. (Box-folder 1/48)
      - Dobbs, Farrell, 1941-1980, n.d. (Box-folder 1/49-56)
      - Dobbs, Marvel, 1944-1969 (Box-folder 1/57-58)
      - Dobbs, Sharon, Carol and Mary Lou (Box-folder 1/59)
      - Doerr, Augusta (Dolly), 1968-1980, n.d. (Box-folder 1/60)
      - Door, Kenneth, 1965 (Box-folder 1/61)
      - Downs, Larry, 1963, 1983 (Box-folder 1/62)
      - Duggan, Bob, 1985, n.d. (Box-folder 1/63)
      - Dunne, Miles, 1941 (Box-folder 2/1)
      - Dunne, V.R. "Ray", 1957, 1962 (Box-folder 2/2)
      - Ede, Everett, 1970 (Box-folder 2/3)
      - Edwards, Herb M., 1972 (Box-folder 2/4)
      - Engels, 1997 (Box-folder 2/5)
      - Esquire magazine, 1978 (Box-folder 2/6)
      - Evergreen State College. Labor Center, 1991-1994, n.d. (Box-folder 2/7)
      - Fairbanks, Pete, 1972, n.d. (Box-folder 2/8)
      - Frechin, Douglas and Karen, 1994-1996 (Box-folder 2/9)
      - Frosig, George, 1938-1949 (Box-folder 2/10)
      - Furst, Gillian, 1984-1994 (Box-folder 2/11)
      - Gagnon, Dorothy, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 2/12)
      - Gano, Judy, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 2/13)
      - General Drivers, Helpers and Insider Workers Union, Local No. 544, 1942-1947 (Box-folder 2/14)
      - Gerschon, Perry, 1950-1951 (Box-folder 2/15)
      - Glass, Patti, 1966-1992, n.d.; See also Weinreich, Patti. (Box-folder 2/16)
      - Glynn, Huey, 1959-1965 (Box-folder 2/17)
      - Good, Laurel, 1948-1955, 1996 (Box-folder 2/18)
      - Gorton, Slade, 1984-1986 (Box-folder 2/19)
      - Gratz, Louisa, 1997 (Box-folder 2/20)
      - Groves, Gale C., 1952-1953, n.d. (Box-folder 2/21)
      - Gundlach, Jean, 1958, 1996, n.d. (Box-folder 2/22)
      - Gundlud, Sean, 1987 (Box-folder 2/23)
      - Hamel, Clarence, 1942-1943 (Box-folder 2/24)
      - Hansen, Inez and Emil, 1958-1964, n.d. (Box-folder 2/25)
      - Harer, Asher, 1956-1998, n.d. (Box-folder 2/26-29)
      - Hasegawa, Bob (and Committee to Re-elect Bob Hasegawa), 1989, 1994 (Box-folder 2/30)
      - Heatlie, Dave and Jody, 1965-1969 (Box-folder 2/31)
      - Hesiler, Francis, 1956 (Box-folder 2/32)
      - Heyman, Jack, 1987-1997, n.d. (Box-folder 2/33)
      - Hicks, Ed, 1980 (Box-folder 2/34)
      - Hoffa, James R., 1965-1966 (Box-folder 2/35)
      - Holland, Ed, 1966 (Box-folder 2/36)
      - Holler, John, 1980-1988, n.d. (Box-folder 2/37)
      - Honey, Michael, 1991 (Box-folder 2/38)
      - Hopkins, Pat and Mark, 1965-1997, n.d. (Box-folder 2/39)
      - Hudson, Carlos, 1939, 1943 (Box-folder 2/40)
      - ILWU-PMA Benefit Plans, 1976-1998 (Box-folder 2/41)
      - Jackson, Henry M., 1946 (Box-folder 2/42)
      - James, Ralph C. ("Professor James"), 1963-1966 (Box-folder 2/43)
      - Jarman Shoe Company, 1977 (Box-folder 2/44)
      - Jarrett, Sid, 1942, 1945 (Box-folder 2/45)
      - Jeffreys, Fritz, 1949 (Box-folder 2/46)
      - Johnson, Blaine, 1991-1995, n.d. (Box-folder 2/47)
      - Johnson, Roy W. "Bacon", 1964-1965 (Box-folder 2/48)
      - Johnston, Curt, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 2/49)
      - Jones, Everett "Red", 1967 (Box-folder 2/50)
      - Kawamura, Michi, 1964 (Box-folder 2/51)
      - Kerry, Karolyn and Tom, 1966 (Box-folder 2/52)
      - Kiernan, Jim, 1978-1979, n.d. (Box-folder 2/53)
      - Kindred, Steve, 1980 (Box-folder 2/54)
      - Kramer, Shelley, 1979 (Box-folder 2/55)
      - Krieger, Bruce, 1970-1998, n.d. (Box-folder 2/56-57)
      - Labor Center Advisory Committee, 1991 (Box-folder 2/58)
      - Lacey, William J., 1956, 1996 (Box-folder 2/59)
      - Lelli, Philip, n.d. (Box-folder 2/60)
      - Leonard, Tom, 1965 (Box-folder 2/61)
      - Love, M.G., 1943 (Box-folder 2/62)
      - Lovell, Frank, 1950-1997 (Box-folder 2/63-68)
      - Lovell, Joan, 1998 (Box-folder 2/69)
      - Lozoski, Paul, 1945-1949 (Box-folder 2/70)
      - Lozoski, Walter, 1952-1966 (Box-folder 2/71-72)
      - Lucio, Tony, 1952-1954 (Box-folder 2/73)
      - Mack, Charles, Jr. "Sonny", 1998, n.d. (Box-folder 2/74)
      - Mack, Margaret "Marge" and Charles, Sr., 1941, 1961 (Box-folder 2/75)
      - Mack, Midge, 1997 (Box-folder 2/76)
      - Magden, Ron, 1993 (Box-folder 2/77)
      - Mahoney, John, 1935-1996 (Box-folder 3/1-3)
      - Mattingly, Bob, 1992-1994 (Box-folder 3/4)
      - Mayo Clinic, 1956-1958 (Box-folder 3/5)
      - McKenzie, Gladys, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 3/6)
      - Miller, Gwen, 1957-1990, n.d. (Box-folder 3/7)
      - Miller, Louis "Lou", 1942-1979 (Box-folder 3/8-16)
      - Miller, Louis Jr. "Tony", 1957, 1991 (Box-folder 3/17)
      - Miller, Marvel Kummer, 1957-1966, 1980 (Box-folder 3/18)
      - Mills, Herb, 1975-1998, n.d. (Box-folder 3/19)
      - Mink, Art, 1965, n.d. (Box-folder 3/20)
      - Moork, Dick, 1963-1995, n.d. (Box-folder 3/21)
      - Moreau, Larry, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 3/22)
      - Morgan, Robert W. and family, 1949-1950 (Box-folder 3/23)
      - Murname, Francis, 1966-1968 (Box-folder 3/24)
      - Murray, Robert "Bob", 1975-1993, n.d. (Box-folder 3/25-27)
      - National Organization of Master Mates and Pilots of America, 1946, n.d. (Box-folder 3/28)
      - Nelson, Burt, 1972-1983 (Box-folder 3/29)
      - New York City Central Labor Council. Shorter Work Week and Automation Committee, 1962 (Box-folder 3/30)
      - Newton, Sharon Weinreich, 1964-1969, n.d. (Box-folder 3/31)
      - Norton, James, 1991-1992, n.d. (Box-folder 3/32)
      - Oster, Harry, 1946-1955. n.d. (Box-folder 3/33)
      - Otis, John, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 3/34)
      - Pacific Maritime Association, 1962 (Box-folder 3/35)
      - Paff, Eugene, 1950-1962, n.d. (Box-folder 3/36-37)
      - Palmquist, Rose, 1975-1996, n.d. (Box-folder 3/38)
      - Palomino Lopez, Angel, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 3/39)
      - Parker, Harry, 1950-1952 (Box-folder 3/40)
      - Phillips, Diane, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 3/41)
      - Pioneer Publishers, 1950-1965 (Box-folder 3/42)
      - Piper, Frank, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 3/43)
      - Poth, Philip, 1944-1955 (Box-folder 3/44)
      - Rachleff, Peter, 1993, n.d. (Box-folder 3/45)
      - Ransome, John "Sarge", 1961-1985, n.d. (Box-folder 3/46-47)
      - Riehle, Dave, 1985-1998, n.d. (Box-folder 3/48-50)
      - Rohrscheib, Luke and Louise, 1982, 1996, n.d. (Box-folder 4/1)
      - Rooke, Rob, 1987-1990 (Box-folder 4/2)
      - Roseland, Bernice, 1942-1947,n.d. (Box-folder 4/3-6)
      - Rosenberg, Sam, 1984, 1996 (Box-folder 4/7)
      - Rousch, M.E. "Rusty" and Ma, 1941-1966 (Box-folder 4/8)
      - Rubio, Rudy, 1982-1985, n.d. (Box-folder 4/9)
      - Russel, Alfred "Greek", 1943-1975 (Box-folder 4/10)
      - Scholl, Clifford, 1962, 1965 (Box-folder 4/11)
      - Scholl, Reuben, 1943 (Box-folder 4/12)
      - Schroeter, Leonard, 1960-1973, 1998, n.d (Box-folder 4/13-14)
      - Selloria, Priscilla "Sally", 1949-1958 (Box-folder 4/15)
      - Severson, Donald, 1939-1996, n.d. (Box-folder 4/16-17)
      - Severson, Donald, family, 1944-1964, n.d. (Box-folder 4/18)
      - Severson, Donna, 1975-1997 (Box-folder 4/19)
      - Severson, Elizabeth "Betty", 1940-1969 (Box-folder 4/20)
      - Severson, James "Jim", 1936-1983 (Box-folder 4/21-22)
      - Severson, Katherine, 1941-1952 (Box-folder 4/23)
      - Severson, Ole, 1946-1948 (Box-folder 4/24)
      - Shaw, Rita, 1984-1988, n.d. (Box-folder 4/25)
      - Sholl, Michele "Micki" (Severson), 1950-1994, n.d. (Box-folder 4/26)
      - Sholl, Wendy, 1982-1985, n.d. (Box-folder 4/27)
      - Skoglund, Carl, 1954, 1960 (Box-folder 4/28)
      - Slater, W.K., n.d. (Box-folder 4/29)
      - Snyder, Fred "Fritz", 1965-1973, 1991 (Box-folder 4/30)
      - Souza, Ralph, 1966-1998 (Box-folder 4/31)
      - Sparrow, Ray, 1956-1965 (Box-folder 4/32)
      - Stiles, Warren, 1950 (Box-folder 4/33)
      - Synestby, Helen, 1944-1964, n.d. (Box-folder 4/34)
      - Synestby, Jane, Kristi, and Ruby, 1944-1964, n.d. (Box-folder 4/35)
      - Takeda, Nobuko, 1949-1950 (Box-folder 4/36)
      - Tarcliff, Hank and Georgia, 1948, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 4/37)
      - Teamsters for a Democratic Union, 1989-1995 (Box-folder 4/38)
      - Trainor, Larry and Gustie, 1945-1997 (Box-folder 4/39)
      - Turtletaub, Carole, 1969 (Box-folder 4/40)
      - UAW-CIO, Ford Local 600 (Box-folder 4/41)
      - U.S. Coast Guard, 1951-1954, n.d. (Box-folder 4/42)
      - U.S. Justice Department, 1946 (Box-folder 4/43)
      - U.S. Labor Department, 1953, 1964 (Box-folder 4/44)
      - U.S. War Shipping Administration, 1943 (Box-folder 4/45)
      - Uran, Don, 1948-1953 (Box-folder 4/46)
      - Uran, Marshall, 1992-1997 (Box-folder 4/47)
      - Valenzuela, Al, n.d. (Box-folder 4/48)
      - Vukich, Pat, 1988, 1995, n.d. (Box-folder 4/49)
      - Walthew, John, 1950-1953 (Box-folder 4/50)
      - Ward, Robert, 1964 (Box-folder 4/51)
      - Weinreich, Alfred Jr., Sharon, and family, 1956-1964 (Box-folder 4/52)
      - Weinreich, Dorothy, 1952-1997, n.d. (Box-folder 4/53-54)
      - Weinreich, Hugh, 1964 (Box-folder 4/55)
      - Weinreich, Michael, 1964 (Box-folder 4/56)
      - Weinreich, Patti (Box-folder 4/57)
      - Weinreich, Robert, 1964, 1985, n.d. (Box-folder 4/58)
      - Weinreich, Sharon, 1959-1964, n.d.; See also Newton, Sharon. (Box-folder 5/1)
      - Weinreich, Susie, 1964 (Box-folder 5/2)
      - Weinreich, Theodore, 1963 (Box-folder 5/3)
      - Weir, Stan, 1985-1994 (Box-folder 5/4)
      - Williams, David, 1961 (Box-folder 5/5)
      - Windoffer, Melba, 1971-1986 (Box-folder 5/6)
      - Wing, Larry, 1970-1982, n.d. (Box-folder 5/7)
      - Wirth, John "Jack" and Genevieve, 1948-1984 (Box-folder 5/8)
      - Wooding, Kenneth, 1961 (Box-folder 5/9)
      - Yamamoto, Yoshiko "June", 1949-1957, n.d. (Box-folder 5/10-11)
      - Zeiger, Bernard, 1969, 1974 (Box-folder 5/12)
      - Zehnder, Cindy, 1982-1986 (Box-folder 5/13)
      - Miscellaneous A, 1944-1997, n.d. (Box-folder 5/14)
      - B, 1953-1992, n.d. (Box-folder 5/15)
      - C, 1940-1998, n.d. (Box-folder 5/16)
      - D, 1944-1994 (Box-folder 5/17)
      - E, 1968-1984 (Box-folder 5/18)
      - G, 1962-1982, n.d. (Box-folder 5/19)
      - H, 1948-1992, n.d. (Box-folder 5/20)
      - I, 1947-1998 (Box-folder 5/21)
      - J, 1938-1991 (Box-folder 5/22)
      - K, 1965-1997, n.d. (Box-folder 5/23)
      - L, 1953-1995, n.d. (Box-folder 5/24)
      - M, 1951-1998, n.d. (Box-folder 5/25)
      - N, 1961-1993, n.d. (Box-folder 5/26)
      - O, 1948-1991, n.d. (Box-folder 5/27)
      - P, 1961-1993, n.d. (Box-folder 5/28)
      - R, 1950-1988, n.d. (Box-folder 5/29)
      - Sa-Se, 1942-1995, n.d. (Box-folder 5/30)
      - Sh-Su, 1938-1994, n.d. (Box-folder 5/31)
      - T, 1947-1984, n.d. (Box-folder 5/32)
      - U, 1948-1996, n.d. (Box-folder 5/33)
      - V, 1966, n.d. (Box-folder 5/34)
      - W, 1951-1996, n.d. (Box-folder 5/35)
      - Y, 1951, 1981, n.d. (Box-folder 5/36)
      - First name only, 1946-1995, n.d. (Box-folder 5/37)
      - Recipient unknown, 1978-1996, n.d. (Box-folder 5/38)
      - Sender unknown (Box-folder 5/39)
      - Davenport Small Claims, 1980 (Box-folder 5/40)
      - Travelers Insurance Co., 1954 (Box-folder 5/41)
      - Re: Elizabeth Severson, 1969 (Box-folder 5/42)
    - Financial Records, 1942-1956, 1995, n.d. (Box-folder 5/43-51)
    - Medical Records, 1939-1987, n.d. (Box-folder 5/52-57)
    - Transcripts (of Interviews), 1987 (Box-folder 5/58)
    - Transcripts (of Interviews) with Others
      - Dobbs, Farrell, 1976 (Box-folder 5/59)
      - Godfredson, Svend, 1976, 1986 (Box-folder 5/60)
      - Welch, Robert, 1961 (Box-folder 5/61)
    - Logs, 1939 (Box-folder 5/62)
    - Court Papers
      - Schneider v. Roland & U.S.C.G., 1967 (Box-folder 5/63)
      - Stark v. Lockheed Shipbuilding and Construction, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 5/64)
      - McCracken v. Babcock & Wilcox, 1977 (Box-folder 5/65)
    - Speeches and Writings
      - "A Tribute: Farrell Dobbs and Marvel Scholl", 1984 (Box-folder 5/66)
      - "Jack Wirth, 1930s Teamster Organizer", 1978 (Box-folder 5/67)
      - "The 1934 Strikes and What Needs To Be Done Today", 1994 (Box-folder 5/68)
      - Miscellaneous Tributes, 1984 (Box-folder 5/69)
    - Speeches and Writings of Others
      - Almeida, Art, 1984, 1992 (Box-folder 6/1)
      - Arneson, Eric, 1987 (Box-folder 6/2)
      - Dembo, Jonathan, 1986 (Box-folder 6/3)
      - Dobbs, Farrell, 1963-1979, n.d. (Box-folder 6/4-5)
      - Expelled SWP Members, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 6/6)
      - Fraser, Clara, 1972 (Box-folder 6/7)
      - Goodman, Irvin and John Caughlan, 1950 (Box:oversize 34)
      - Harer, Asher, 1993 (Box-folder 6/8)
      - Kling, Howard, 1996 (Box-folder 6/9)
      - Lang, Frederick [i.e., Frank Lovell], 1943 (Box-folder 6/10)
      - Lovell, Frank, 1973-1997, n.d. (Box-folder 6/11-12)
      - McCloud, Janet, 1978 (Box-folder 6/13)
      - Moody, Kim, n.d. (Box-folder 6/14)
      - Rachleff, Peter, 1986, 1991-1996 (Box-folder 6/15)
      - Redfield, Sandra, 1984 (Box-folder 6/16)
      - Riehle, David, 1992-1994 (Box-folder 6/17)
      - Schlossberg, Stephen, 1994 (Box-folder 6/18)
      - Walker, Charles, 1985, 1994-1996 (Box-folder 6/19)
      - Weir, Stan, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 6/20)
      - Wells and Stodder (Box-folder 6/21)
      - Yeghissian, Patricia, 1975-1978 (Box-folder 6/22)
      - Miscellaneous and Unknown Authors, 1974-1996, n.d. (Box-folder 6/23)
    - Manuscripts of Others
      - Dobbs, Farrell, 1972-1979 (Box-folder 6/24-31)
      - Magden, Ron, 1991 (Box-folder 6/32-33)
      - Unknown, n.d. (Box-folder 6/34)
    - Conference and Convention Files, 1995 (Box-folder 6/35)
    - Subject Series
      - BRAC, 1981 (Box-folder 6/36)
      - Boycott, 1991, n.d. (Box-folder 6/37)
      - Centralia Mural Project, 1997; Includes oversized poster. (Box-folder 6/38)
      - Convoy to Russia, 1992, n.d. (Box-folder 6/39)
      - Cuba/Castro, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 7/1)
      - Davis Tour, 1958 (Box-folder 7/2)
      - El Salvador, 1981 (Box-folder 7/3)
      - Grain Belt, 1975 (Box-folder 7/4)
      - Hoffa Film, 1992 (Box-folder 7/5)
      - Impeachment, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 7/6)
      - Ind[ependent] Soc[ialist] Data, 1958 (Box-folder 7/7)
      - IWW Songs, n.d. (Box-folder 7/8)
      - Initiative 394, 1981, n.d. (Box-folder 7/9)
      - John's [i.e., John Mahoney's] case, 1957-1961, n.d. (Box-folder 7/10-11)
      - Lori Lakshas, 1976 (Box-folder 7/12)
      - Mahoney v. State of Alaska, 1975-1978 (Box-folder 7/13)
      - Maloney v. ESD, 1952-1956 (Box-folder 7/14)
      - Maloney v. Johnson Line, 1953-1957 (Box-folder 7/15)
      - Maloney v. PMA, 1977-1979 (Box-folder 7/16-20)
      - NMU Manning, 1952 (Box-folder 7/21)
      - Public Health Care Coalition, 1971 (Box-folder 7/22)
      - P-9, 1986-1987, n.d. (Box-folder 7/23)
      - SWP v. FBI, 1950, 1981 (Box-folder 7/24)
      - SWP-related Matters, 1948-1963, n.d. (Box-folder 7/25)
      - U. Com, 1950-1955 (Box-folder 7/26)
      - Washington State Labor Council, 1996 (Box-folder 7/27)
    - Clippings
    - Publications
      - Against the Current; Atwesasne Notes (Box-folder 7/40)
      - American Labor, 1983-1986 (Box-folder 7/41)
      - American Socialist, 1955-1959 (Box-folder 7/42)
      - Bulletin in Defense of Marxism, 1984-1991 (Box-folder 7/43-44)
      - Bulletin of International Socialism, 1964-1966 (Box-folder 7/45)
      - Bulletin of the Open World Conference for the World Workers International, 1991 (Box-folder 7/46)
      - Convergence, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 7/47)
      - Dissent, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 7/48)
      - Dollars and Sense, 1977-1987 (Box-folder 8/1)
      - Forum; Fact, 1966, 1983 (Box-folder 8/2)
      - Freedom Socialists, 1981, 1984, 1991 (Box-folder 8/3)
      - Guardian, The, 1983 (Box-folder 8/4)
      - Honduras; Independent Political News, 1984, 1998 (Box-folder 8/5)
      - Industrial Worker, 1974-1983 (Box-folder 8/6)
      - Internal Information Bulletin, 1952, 1964, 1989 (Box-folder 8/7)
      - International Socialist Review, 1983 (Box-folder 8/8)
      - LPON Newsletter, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 8/9)
      - Labor Education & Research Project Publications, 1979, n.d. (Box-folder 8/10)
      - Labor Notes, 1980-1998 (Box-folder 8/11-12)
      - Labor's Voice, 1996-1998 (Box-folder 8/13)
      - El Malcrido, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 8/14)
      - Michigan Militant, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 8/15)
      - Militant, 1956-1996 (Box-folder 8/16)
      - Mill Hunk Herald, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 8/17)
      - Organizer, 1991, 1996 (Box-folder 8/18)
      - Official Year Book of Organized Labor, 1932 (Box:oversize 34)
      - Pacific Peacemaker, 1984 (Box-folder 8/19)
      - Peoples World, 1985-1997 (Box-folder 8/20)
      - Pioneer Publishers Publications, 1947-1957, n.d. (Box-folder 8/21)
      - Radical Women Publications, 1973-1980 (Box-folder 8/22)
      - SWP Discussion Bulletin, 1963 (Box-folder 8/23)
      - Solidarity Organizing Committee, 1991-1995 (Box-folder 8/24)
      - UAW Solidarity, 1962 (Box-folder 8/25)
      - Union Advocate, 1996-1998 (Box-folder 8/26)
      - United Irishman, 1975 (Box-folder 8/27)
      - United World Organizer, 1978 (Box-folder 8/28)
      - West Coast Sailors, 1950-1997 (incomplete) (Box-folder 8B)
      - U.S. Department of Labor Publications, 1956-1968 (Box-folder 8/29)
      - Miscellaneous, 1957-1997, n.d. (Box-folder 8/30-39)
    - Pamphlets, 1986, n.d. (Box-folder 8/40)
    - Newsletters
      - Bulletin of Citizen's Emergency Committee for Kerbiozen, 1961 (Box-folder 8/41)
      - Irish Republican Movement, 1973 (Box-folder 8/42)
      - Sanity Now, 1973 (Box-folder 8/43)
      - Politics for Workers, 1977 (Box-folder 8/44)
      - Committee for Justice for Domingo and Viernes, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 8/45)
      - Women in the Workforce, 1983 (Box-folder 8/46)
    - Flyers, 1949-1998, n.d. (Box-folder 8/47-50)
    - Maps, n.d. (Box-folder 8/51)
    - Calenders, 1969-1988 (Box-folder 8/52)
    - Business Cards, n.d. (Box-folder 9/1)
    - Notes, 1996, n.d. (Box-folder 9/2-4)
    - Photographs, 1933-1996, n.d. (Box-folder 9/5-9)
    - Photographs, n.d. (Box:oversize 33)
    - Ephemera (Box-folder 9/10-12)
  - American Civil Liberties Union. Southern California Branch
    - General Correspondence, 1950-1953 (Box-folder 9/13)
    - Newsletters, 1950-1952 (Box-folder 9/14-15)
  - Irish Heritage Club, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 9/16)
  - Labor Party Advocate
    - General Correspondence, 1992-1996, n.d. (Box-folder 9/17)
    - Miscellany, 1992-1996, n.d. (Box-folder 9/18)
    - Publications, 1992-1997 (Box-folder 9/19-20)
  - Marine Workers Historical Association, 1993-1999 (Box-folder 9/21-22)
  - Northwest Committee Against Repressive Legislation, 1967, 1972 (Box-folder 9/23)
  - Pacific Coast Maritime History Committee, 1995-1997 (Box-folder 9/24)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America
    - Organizational Features, 1947-1994, n.d. (Box-folder 9/25-28)
    - General Correspondence, 1991-1996 (Box-folder 9/29)
    - Outgoing Letters (of Others)
      - International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 9/30)
      - Teamsters for a Democratic Union, 1993 (Box-folder 9/31)
      - Miscellaneous, 1978-1994 (Box-folder 9/32)
    - Agreements, 1970-1994, n.d. (Box-folder 9/33-35)
    - Resolutions, n.d. (Box-folder 9/36)
    - Reports, 1961-1996 (Box-folder 9/37-41)
    - Speeches and Writings (of Others)
      - Benson, Herman, 1992 (Box-folder 9/42)
      - Hammer, Richard, 1974 (Box-folder 9/43)
      - Hitts, Brian, n.d. (Box-folder 9/44)
      - James, Ralph and Estelle, 1963 (Box-folder 9/45)
      - Leiter, Robert, 1957 (Box-folder 9/46)
      - Lens, Sidney, 1956 (Box-folder 9/47)
      - Walker, Charles, 1994 (Box-folder 9/48)
      - Williams, Tony and Martinez, Selvio (Box-folder 9/49)
      - Memoranda, 1978 (Box-folder 9/50)
    - Campaign Material, 1983 (Box-folder 9/51)
    - Publications
      - Convoy Dispatch, 1981-1995 (Box-folder 9/52-53)
      - Highway Evangelist, 1975 (Box-folder 9/54)
      - History of the Western Conference of Teamsters, n.d. (Box-folder 9/55)
      - Local 174 Teamsters Times, 1992-1998 (Box-folder 9/56)
      - Prod Dispatch, 1978 (Box-folder 9/57)
      - TDU-10 Years and Going Strong, 1985 (Box-folder 9/58)
      - Cleaning Up Our Union, Building Teamster Clout, 1995 (Box-folder 9/59)
      - Miscellaneous, 1953-1964 (Box-folder 9/60)
    - Newsletters
      - TDU, 1983-1994 (Box-folder 9/61)
      - TDU Evergreen Chapter, 1988-1996 (Box-folder 9/62)
      - Miscellaneous, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 9/63)
    - Press Releases, 1994 (Box-folder 9/64)
    - Conferences and Conventions, 1994 (Box-folder 9/65)
    - Training Material, n.d. (Box-folder 9/66)
    - Flyers, 1972-1996, n.d. (Box-folder 9/67-69)
    - Notes, 1994, n.d. (Box-folder 9/70-72)
    - Subject Series
      - 174 Election, Sept. 1994 (Box-folder 9/73)
      - 174 Election, Nov.-Dec. 1994 (Box-folder 9/74)
      - Container Rider, 1981 (Box-folder 9/75)